[

](https://recrypt.app/)

Privacy Policy
==============

Our privacy policy sets out how Recrypt Limited (“Recrypt”) uses and protects any information that you give us when you visit and use our website. Recrypt is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and any information you provide when using our website will only be used in the ways outlined in this privacy policy.

### What we collect

We collect the following information from visitors to our website via the ways identified below:

* Contact Form – your name, your email address, and the nature of your enquiry.

### What we do with the information we gather

The information obtained from you on submission of any forms on this website will be carefully assessed, forwarded onto the most relevant person or department in our organisation and appropriate action is taken.  The safety and security of your data is important to us and it will be kept secure.

If you have supplied us with your email address to keep you updated with our news, we will use your information for this purpose only.

We will not sell, distribute, or lease your personal information to third parties.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure and in order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect via our website.

### Google Analytics

In order to track visitors to our website and identify which pages they are interested in, we use a third-party service called Google Analytics to collect this type of information.  The information obtained does not identify anyone.

### Hotjar Analytics

We use Hotjar to help us understand how users navigate around individual pages on our site. We also use this software to create questionnaires to gather user feedback. Further information on how Hotjar uses cookies can be found on the [Hotjar website](http://inside.hotjar.com/support/solutions/articles/1000132900-what-cookies-does-hotjar-store-on-my-visitors-browsers-).

### Controlling your personal information

Recrypt will not disclose your personal data without consent.

If you have previously supplied us with your email address so that we may keep you updated about our news and you change your mind, please email [hello@recrypt.app](mailto:hello@recrypt.app) or write to us at Recrypt, Cunard Two Suite, The Cotton Exchange, Bixteth Street, Liverpool, L3 9LQ and we will remove your details immediately upon receipt.

If you wish to see details of personal information which we hold about you, you may submit a subject access request under Data Protection Act 1998.  If you would like a copy of the information held on you, please write to Recrypt, Cunard Two Suite, The Cotton Exchange, Bixteth Street, Liverpool, L3 9LQ.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email [hello@recrypt.app](mailto:hello@recrypt.app) or write to us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance to our terms of use, privacy, and cookies policies. Recrypt regularly reviews its policies to ensure they continue to meet current legislative requirements and the needs of our business.

_Last updated on 17/07/2020_

Interested in our product?

Follow us on social media

* [
    
    ](https://www.facebook.com/RecryptApp "Facebook")
* [
    
    ](https://www.instagram.com/recryptapp/ "Instagram")
* [
    
    ](https://twitter.com/RecryptApp "Twitter")

Copyright © 2024 Recrypt
